{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A binary relationship is which of the following?", "opta": "A relationship between two attributes", "optb": "A relationship between two entities", "optc": "An attribute with two different relationships", "optd": "An entity with two different relationships", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If there are two entities with a relationship between them, and one of the entities is completely dependent on the other, then which of the following must exist?", "opta": "Derived attribute", "optb": "Optional one cardinality", "optc": "Multi-valued attribute", "optd": "Weak entity", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A relationship is which of the following?", "opta": "A person, place, or thing", "optb": "Property or characteristic of an entity", "optc": "Link between entities", "optd": "Weak entity", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following conditions should exist if you want to convert a relationship to an associative entity?", "opta": "Some of the relationships for the participating entities are \"many\".", "optb": "The resulting associative entity has an independent meaning.", "optc": "The resulting associative entity has no attributes.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A good identifier is which of the following?", "opta": "One that can change over time", "optb": "Can be null", "optc": "One that is unique", "optd": "Be intelligent", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A rectangle represents which of the following in an ERD?", "opta": "Attribute", "optb": "Entity", "optc": "Optional One", "optd": "Relationship", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An entity name should be which of the following?", "opta": "A singular noun", "optb": "Specific to the organization", "optc": "Concise", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An oval represents which of the following in an ERD?", "opta": "Attribute", "optb": "Entity", "optc": "Optional One", "optd": "Relationship", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When the minimum and maximum number of instances of an entity is one, you know which of the following?", "opta": "Mandatory one", "optb": "Optional one", "optc": "Mandatory many", "optd": "Cannot tell", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An attribute name should be which of the following?", "opta": "Singular verb or verb phrase", "optb": "Follow a standard format", "optc": "Use a alias", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A composite attribute is which of the following?", "opta": "An attribute that can be broken into components", "optb": "An attribute that cannot be broken into components", "optc": "Multiple attributes", "optd": "An identifier", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A binary relationship cannot be which of the following?", "opta": "One-to-One", "optb": "One-to-Many", "optc": "Many-to-Many", "optd": "Zero-to-Zero", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A ternary relationship involves how many entities?", "opta": "3 or less", "optb": "3", "optc": "More than 3", "optd": "3 or more", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When the minimum number of instances of an entity is one, you know which of the following?", "opta": "Mandatory one", "optb": "Optional one", "optc": "Mandatory many", "optd": "Cannot tell", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A good business rule is which of the following?", "opta": "Declarative", "optb": "Imprecise", "optc": "Redundant", "optd": "Compound", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}